Guide to the Harvey Williams Cushing Papers in the Yale University Library
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Papers held in Manuscripts and Archives, Part I
  - Correspondence, 1884-1939; Series I; 29 linear feet (70 boxes, 55 reels)
    - Royal Society of Medicine, 1919-1932 (Box 56, Folder 1238, Reel 45)
    - Royce Club, 1916-1927 (Box 56, Folder 1239, Reel 45)
    - Royle, Norman D., 1924-1938 (Box 56, Folder 1240, Reel 45)
    - Royster, Hubert A., 1917-1938 (Box 57, Folder 1241, Reel 45)
      See also: Series II, Folders 387-388
    - Rubens, Ruth
      See: Series II, Folder 746
    - Rush, Charles E., 1935-1936 (Box 57, Folder 1242, Reel 46)
    - Rushmore, Stephen, 1919-1922 (Box 57, Folder 1243, Reel 46)
    - Ryerson, E. Stanley
    - Sab-Sal (Box 57, Folder 1244, Reel 46)
    - Sam-Say (Box 57, Folder 1245, Reel 46)
    - Sca-Scho (Box 57, Folder 1246, Reel 46)
    - Schr-Scr (Box 57, Folder 1247, Reel 46)
    - Se (Box 57, Folder 1248, Reel 46)
    - Sha-Shep (Box 57, Folder 1249, Reel 46)
    - Sher-Sim (Box 57, Folder 1250, Reel 46)
    - Sin-Sl (Box 57, Folder 1251, Reel 46)
    - Sm (Box 57, Folder 1252, Reel 46)
    - Sn-So (Box 57, Folder 1253, Reel 46)
    - Sp-Sq (Box 57, Folder 1254, Reel 46)
    - Sta-Ste (Box 58, Folder 1255, Reel 47)
    - Sti-Sto (Box 58, Folder 1256, Reel 47)
    - Str-Stu (Box 58, Folder 1257, Reel 47)
    - Su (Box 58, Folder 1258, Reel 47)
    - Sv-Sy (Box 58, Folder 1259, Reel 47)
    - Sachs, Bernard, 1905, 1916, 1925-1938 (Box 58, Folder 1260, Reel 47)
      See also: Series II, Folders 190, 242, 466
    - Sachs, Ernest, 1916-1938 (Box 58, Folder 1261, Reel 47)
    - Sa'di, Lufti F., 1931-1938 (Box 58, Folder 1262, Reel 47)
    - Sa'eed, M., 1927-1930 (Box 58, Folder 1263, Reel 47)
      See also: Series II, Folder 594
    - Sa'eed, M., 1932-1939 (Box 58, Folder 1264, Reel 47)
    - Saffo, Paul L., 1935-1937 (Box 58, Folder 1265, Reel 47)
      See also: Series II, Folder 770
    - St. John, Fordyce B., 1920-1933 (Box 58, Folder 1266, Reel 47)
    - St. John, William H., 1891, 1930-1939 (Box 58, Folder 1267, Reel 47)
    - Saito, Makoto, 1929-1936 (Box 58, Folder 1268, Reel 47)
    - Salmon, Thomas W., 1919-1927 (Box 58, Folder 1269, Reel 47)
      See also: Folder 1039
    - Salmon Memorial Committe, Inc., 1929-1938 (Box 58, Folder 1270, Reel 47)
    - Sanborn Agency, 1933-1936 (Box 58, Folder 1271, Reel 47)
    - Sandiford, Irene, 1916-1929, undated (Box 58, Folder 1272, Reel 47)
    - Sanford, Henry L., 1927 (Box 59, Folder 1273, Reel 47)
      See also: Series II, Folder 192
    - Sare, R. E.
    - Sargent, John Singer, undated (Box 59, Folder 1274, Reel 47)
    - Sarton, George, 1916-1939 (Box 59, Folder 1275, Reel 47)
      See also: Series II, Folder 866
    - Sata, A.
    - Saturday Review, 1925-1929, 1938-1939 (Box 59, Folder 1276, Reel 47)
    - Sauerbruch, F., 1908, 1926, 1935 (Box 59, Folder 1277, Reel 47)
    - Saunders (W. B.) Co., 1915-1939 (Box 59, Folder 1278, Reel 47)
    - Sawyer, Charles J.
    - Sayle, Charles
    - Scarff, John E., 1930-1931, 1937 (Box 59, Folder 1279, Reel 47)
      See also: Series II, Folders 462, 770
    - Schäfer, Edward A., 1908-1915 (Box 59, Folder 1280, Reel 47)
      See also: Folder 1305
    - Schaltenbrand, Georges, 1927-1938 (Box 59, Folder 1281, Reel 47)
      See also: Series II, Folder 826
    - Schlaepfer, Karl, 1920-1925, undated (Box 59, Folder 1282, Reel 47)
    - Schlesinger, Benno, 1928, 1932-1934 (Box 59, Folder 1283, Reel 47)
    - Schlesinger, Benno, 1935-1937 (Box 59, Folder 1284, Reel 47)
    - Schlesinger, Benno, 1938 (Box 59, Folder 1285, Reel 47)
    - Schlesinger, Benno, 1939 (Box 59, Folder 1286, Reel 48)
    - Schlueter, Robert E., 1936-1939 (Box 59, Folder 1287, Reel 48)
    - Schneekloth, Gustav, 1933-1939 (Box 59, Folder 1288, Reel 48)
      See also: Series II, Folders 179-184
    - Schneller, M. R.
    - Schnitker, Max T., 1936-1938 (Box 59, Folder 1289, Reel 48)
    - Scholar's Facsimiles and Reprints, 1936-1939 (Box 59, Folder 1290, Reel 48)
    - Schönbauer, Leopold, 1925, 1931- 1937 (Box 59, Folder 1291, Reel 48)
    - Schreiber, Frederic, 1929-1939 (Box 59, Folder 1292, Reel 48)
    - Schreiber, John P., 1924-1925 (Box 59, Folder 1293, Reel 48)
    - Schubert, Margaret R., 1933-1939 (Box 59, Folder 1294, Reel 48)
    - Schueck, Franz
    - Schuman, Henry
      See: Series II, Folder 894
    - Schuman's
      See: Series II, Folder 140
    - Schwab, Sidney I., 1908-1930 (Box 59, Folder 1295, Reel 48)
      See also: Folder 1038
    - Schwartz, R. Plato, 1922-1929, 1938 (Box 59, Folder 1296, Reel 48)
    - Schwarz, Ignaz
      See: Series II, Folders 141-142
    - Schwarz, Kurt L.
    - Schweinitz, George E. de, 1912-1916, 1923-1931 (Box 59, Folder 1297, Reel 48)
      See also: Series II, Folder 596
    - Scott, W. J. Merle, 1924-1932 (Box 59, Folder 1298, Reel 48)
      See also: Folder 1334; Series II, Folders 355, 440-441, 444
    - Scribner, Charles
      See: Series II, Folder 143
    - Scroll and Key, 1891-1893 (Box 59, Folder 1299, Reel 48)
    - Scudder, Charles L., 1892, 1910- 1934 (Box 59, Folder 1300, Reel 48)
    - Sears, George G.
    - Sedgwick, Ellery, 1916-1936 (Box 59, Folder 1301, Reel 48)
    - Severinghaus, A. E., 1932-1933, 1939 (Box 59, Folder 1302, Reel 48)
      See also: Series II, Folder 461
    - Seymour, Charles, 1935-1939 (Box 59, Folder 1303, Reel 48)
    - Shamoff, V. N., 1914-1924 (Box 59, Folder 1304, Reel 48)
    - Sharpey-Schafer, Sir Edward Sharpey-Schafer, Lady Maude, 1920-1933 (Box 60, Folder 1305, Reel 48)
      See also: Folder 1280, Series II Folder 469
    - Shattuck, Frederick C., 1916-1928 (Box 60, Folder 1306, Reel 48)
      See also: Series II, Folders 245, 386, 438, 440, 442, 445-446, 597, 775
    - Shattuck, George C., 1919-1939 (Box 60, Folder 1306a, Reel 48)
    - Shattuck, Henry L.
      See: Folder 1036
    - Sheehan, Edward, 1931-1934 (Box 60, Folder 1307, Reel 48)
    - Sheeler, K. L.
      See: Series II, Folder 728
    - Shenton, Herbert H.
      See: Series II, Folder 942
    - Sheperd, Francis J.
      See: Series II, Folder 598
    - Shepley, George F.
    - Shepley, Henry R., 1927-1935 (Box 60, Folder 1308, Reel 48)
      See also: Series II, Folders 15-17
    - Shepley, Julia
      See: Folder 1249; Series II, Folder 599
    - Sherman, Edward A., 1933-1936 (Box 60, Folder 1309, Reel 48)
    - Sherrill, Charles H., 1927-1929 (Box 60, Folder 1310, Reel 48)
    - Sherrington, Sir Charles Scott Sherrington, Lady Ethel, 1916-1939 (Box 60, Folder 1311, Reel 48)
      See also: Series II, Folders 188, 594, 864; MHL
    - Shipley, Arthur E.
      See: Series II, Folder 594
    - Shiras, Winfield
    - Shreiber, Frederic
      See: Series II, Folder 671
    - Shreve, Crump and Low Co., 1922-1923 (Box 60, Folder 1312, Reel 48)
    - Shyrock, Richard H., 1936-1937 (Box 60, Folder 1313, Reel 48)
    - Sigerist, Henry E., 1927-1935 (Box 60, Folder 1314, Reel 48)
    - Simmons, George H., 1909, 1919- 1926 (Box 60, Folder 1315, Reel 48)
      See also: Folders 46-47; Series II, Folders 594, 632-634, 639, 865
    - Simpson, S. Levy, 1930-1937 (Box 60, Folder 1316, Reel 48)
    - Simpson, Sutherland
      See: Series II, Folder 463
    - Singer, Charles, 1923-1929 (Box 60, Folder 1317, Reel 48)
      See also: Series II, Folders 296, 866, 908
    - Sisson, Warren R., 1916, 1928, 1932 (Box 60, Folder 1318, Reel 48)
    - Sizer, Theodore, 1934-1939 (Box 60, Folder 1319, Reel 48)
      See also: Series II, Folder 235
    - Sloan, Elmer
      See: Series II, Folder 28
    - Sluder, Greenfield, 1919-1923 (Box 60, Folder 1320, Reel 48)
    - Smith, G. Elliot, 1929-1935 (Box 60, Folder 1321, Reel 48)
    - Smith, George M., 1924, 1937-1939, n.d (Box 60, Folder 1322, Reel 48)
      See also: Series II, Folder 652
    - Smith, Harrison
      See: Series II, Folder 652
    - Smith, Phillip E., 1921-1935 (Box 60, Folder 1323, Reel 48)
    - Smith, Richard R.
      See: Series II, Folder 651
    - Smith, Winford H., 1914-1922, 1927 (Box 60, Folder 1324, Reel 48)
      See also: Series II, Folders 490, 600
    - Smith-Petersen, M. N., 1925-1931 (Box 60, Folder 1325, Reel 48)
    - Smithsonian Institution, 1927-1928, 1933-1938 (Box 60, Folder 1326, Reel 48)
    - Société Française d'Histoire de la Médecine, 1913, 1920-1938 (Box 60, Folder 1327, Reel 48)
    - Société Internationale de Chirurgie: Congress of 1923, 1921-1925 (Box 60, Folder 1328, Reel 48)
    - Society for Savings, 1920-1924, 1929-1933 (Box 60, Folder 1329, Reel 48)
    - Society of British Neurological Surgeons, 1927-1939 (Box 60, Folder 1330, Reel 48)
    - Society of Clinical Surgery, 1905-1911 (Box 60, Folder 1331, Reel 48)
    - Society of Clinical Surgery, 1914-1923 (Box 60, Folder 1332, Reel 48)
    - Society of Clinical Surgery, 1924-1933 (Box 61, Folder 1333, Reel 49)
    - Society of Clinical Surgery, 1934-1939 (Box 61, Folder 1334, Reel 49)
    - Society of Clinical Surgery, undated (Box 61, Folder 1335, Reel 49)
    - Society of Experimental Biology and Medicine, 1924-1929 (Box 61, Folder 1336, Reel 49)
    - Society of Neurological Surgeons, 1919-1921 (Box 61, Folder 1337, Reel 49)
    - Society of Neurological Surgeons, 1922-1923 (Box 61, Folder 1338, Reel 49)
    - Society of Neurological Surgeons, 1924-1925 (Box 61, Folder 1339, Reel 49)
    - Society of Neurological Surgeons, 1926 (Box 61, Folder 1340, Reel 49)
    - Society of Neurological Surgeons, 1927 (Box 61, Folder 1341, Reel 49)
    - Society of Neurological Surgeons, 1928 (Box 61, Folder 1342, Reel 49)
    - Society of Neurological Surgeons, 1929 (Box 61, Folder 1343, Reel 49)
    - Society of Neurological Surgeons, 1930-1933 (Box 61, Folder 1344, Reel 49)
    - Society of Neurological Surgeons, 1934-1939 (Box 61, Folder 1345, Reel 49)
    - Society of the New York Hospital, 1921-1938 (Box 61, Folder 1346, Reel 49)
    - Soper, Willard B.
      See: Series II, Folder 866
    - Soracco, Thomas E.
    - Sosman, Merrill C., 1934-1939 (Box 61, Folder 1347, Reel 49)
      See also: Series II, Folders 671, 783-791
    - Sotheby and Co.
      See: Series II, Folder 144
    - Sotheran, Henry
      See: Series II, Folder 145
    - Southard, E. E., 1910-1923 (Box 61, Folder 1348, Reel 49)
    - Spencer, Frederick Montgomery, 1928-1929 (Box 61, Folder 1349, Reel 49)
    - Spielmann, M. H.
      See: Series II, Folder 906
    - Spies, John W.
      See: Series II, Folders 356, 835
    - Spivack, S. S., 1937-1938 (Box 61, Folder 1350, Reel 49)
    - Spring, Hobart W.
      See: Series II, Folders 179-184
    - Spurling, R. Glen, 1925-1935 (Box 61, Folder 1351, Reel 49)
      See also: Series II, Folder 671
    - Stammers, F. A. R.
      See: Series II, Folder 827
    - Starr, Clarence L. Starr, Annie, 1921-1929 (Box 61, Folder 1352, Reel 49)
      See also: Series II, Folder 812
    - Starr, M. Allen, 1909-1930, undated (Box 61, Folder 1353, Reel 49)
    - Stater, Walter J., 1923-1931 (Box 61, Folder 1354, Reel 49)
    - Stechert and Co.
      See: Series II, Folder 146
    - Steiner, Walter R., 1919-1939 (Box 62, Folder 1355, Reel 49)
    - Stengel, Alfred
      See: Series II, Folder 601
    - Stevens and Brown, Ltd.
      See: Series II, Folders 147-148
    - Stewart, George Stewart, Sarah Klebs, 1935-1939, undated (Box 62, Folder 1356, Reel 49)
    - Stewart, Mrs. Robert W.
    - Stiles, Sir Harold J., 1920-1926 (Box 62, Folder 1357, Reel 49)
      See also: Series II, Folders 188, 811
    - Stiles, Margaret, 1890-1894 (Box 62, Folder 1358, Reel 49)
    - Stimson, Horace P., 1924-1926, 1930-1931, 1936 (Box 62, Folder 1359, Reel 49)
    - Stirling, A. Dickson, 1921-1939 (Box 62, Folder 1360, Reel 49)
    - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1919-1921 (Box 62, Folder 1361, Reel 49)
    - Stone, A. K.
    - Stonehill, C. A.
      See: Series II, Folders 149-150
    - Stookey, Byron, 1927-1931 (Box 62, Folder 1362, Reel 49)
    - Streeter, Edward C., 1914-1923 (Box 62, Folder 1363, Reel 49)
      See also: Series II, Folders 386-387, 389, 595, 907
    - Streeter, Edward C., 1924-1939, undated (Box 62, Folder 1364, Reel 49)
      See also: Series II, Folders 189, 469, 595, 907
    - Strong, Richard P., 1915-1938 (Box 62, Folder 1365, Reel 49)
    - Sturgis, C. C.
      See: Folder 26; Series II, Folders 389, 392
    - Sullivan, Eugene J.
    - Swedish Royal Academy of Science: Nobel Committee, 1915-1939 (Box 62, Folder 1366, Reel 50)
    - Sweet, Forest H.
      See: Series II, Folder 151
    - Swift, W. H.
      See: Series II, Folder 439
    - Sydenstricker, Edgar
      See: Series II, Folders 193-197, 199, 201
    - Symonds, C. P., 1920-1939 (Box 62, Folder 1367, Reel 50)
    - Ta (Box 62, Folder 1368, Reel 50)
    - Te (Box 62, Folder 1369, Reel 50)
    - Th (Box 62, Folder 1370, Reel 50)
    - Ti (Box 62, Folder 1371, Reel 50)
    - To (Box 62, Folder 1372, Reel 50)
    - Tr (Box 62, Folder 1373, Reel 50)
    - Tu (Box 62, Folder 1374, Reel 50)
    - Tw-Ty (Box 63, Folder 1375, Reel 50)
    - Takats, G. de, 1925-1932, undated (Box 63, Folder 1376, Reel 50)
    - Tanaka, Fumio, 1916-1935 (Box 63, Folder 1377, Reel 50)
    - Tarbell, Edmund C., 1908-1909 (Box 63, Folder 1378, Reel 50)
    - Tauber and Weil
      See: Series II, Folders 155-158
    - Tavern Club, 1914-1934 (Box 63, Folder 1379, Reel 50)
    - Taylor, Adrian S., 1923-1932 (Box 63, Folder 1380, Reel 50)
    - Taylor, E. Wyllys, 1908-1932 (Box 63, Folder 1381, Reel 50)
      See also: Folder 202, Series II Folder 885
    - Taylor, Effie J., 1934-1939 (Box 63, Folder 1382, Reel 50)
    - Taylor, Isabella G., 1931 (Box 63, Folder 1383, Reel 50)
    - Taylor, Julian
      See: Series II, Folder 672
    - Taylor, Sir William, 1925-1930 (Box 63, Folder 1384, Reel 50)
    - Teel, Harold M., 1929-1932 (Box 63, Folder 1385, Reel 50)
      See also: Series II, Folders 446-447
    - Templeton, Earl R., 1924-1934 (Box 63, Folder 1386, Reel 50)
    - Thayer, Elizabeth W., 1932-1938 (Box 63, Folder 1387, Reel 50)
    - Thayer, William S., 1899-1933, undated (Box 63, Folder 1388, Reel 50)
      See also: Folder 26, Series II Folders 604, 628-629
    - Thing, Alice, 1928-1935 (Box 63, Folder 1389, Reel 50)
      See also: Series II, Folder 746
    - Thoma, Kurt H., 1932-1938 (Box 63, Folder 1390, Reel 50)
    - Thomas, Charles C., 1927-1928 June (Box 63, Folder 1391, Reel 50)
      See also: Folder 1536
    - Thomas, Charles C., 1928 July-1929 (Box 63, Folder 1392, Reel 50)
    - Thomas, Charles C., 1930-1932 (Box 63, Folder 1393, Reel 50)
      See also: Folder 1536; Series II, 842-845
    - Thomas, Charles C., 1933-1935 (Box 63, Folder 1394, Reel 50)
      See also: Folder 1536; Series II, Folders 471-475, 679-684, 842-845
    - Thomas, Charles C., 1936-1938 (Box 63, Folder 1395, Reel 51)
      See also: Series II, Folders 471-475, 679-684, 842-845
    - Thomas, Charles C., 1939 (Box 63, Folder 1396, Reel 51)
      See also: Series II, Folders 679-684
    - Thomas, Frank G.
      See: Series II, Folder 602
    - Thomas, Henry M.
    - Thompson, C. J. S., 1925-1939 (Box 63, Folder 1397, Reel 51)
    - Thompson, Kenneth Wade, 1933-1937 (Box 63, Folder 1398, Reel 51)
      See also: Series II, Folder 944
    - Thoms, Herbert, 1929-1938, undated (Box 63, Folder 1399, Reel 51)
    - Thomson, J. Oscar, 1921-1925 (Box 63, Folder 1400, Reel 51)
    - Thorndike, Augustus, Jr., 1924-1935 (Box 63, Folder 1401, Reel 51)
      See also: Series II, Folder 814
    - Thorndike, Lynn, 1920-1937 (Box 63, Folder 1402, Reel 51)
    - Thorndike, Paul
      See: Series II, Folders 428-435
    - Tide-Over League, 1926-1935, undated (Box 63, Folder 1403, Reel 51)
    - Tilden, Charles J., 1933-1938 (Box 64, Folder 1404, Reel 51)
    - Tilney, Frederick and Camilla, 1924-1939 (Box 64, Folder 1405, Reel 51)
    - Time, 1923-1939 (Box 64, Folder 1406, Reel 51)
    - Timme, Walter, 1932 (Box 64, Folder 1407, Reel 51)
      See also: Folder 91
    - Tinker, Martin B.
      See: Series II, Folder 814
    - Titus, Paul and Mary Cushing, 1933-1937 (Box 64, Folder 1408, Reel 51)
    - Todd, T. Wingate, 1915-1936 (Box 64, Folder 1409, Reel 51)
    - Tönnis, Wilhelm, 1935-1939 (Box 64, Folder 1410, Reel 51)
    - Towle, Herbert Ladd and Edith, 1936-1938 (Box 64, Folder 1411, Reel 51)
    - Towne, Edward B., 1916-1930, undated (Box 64, Folder 1412, Reel 51)
      See also: Series II, Folders 672, 846
    - Townsend, Howard, 1921, 1926-1931, undated (Box 64, Folder 1413, Reel 51)
    - Townsend, Howard, Jr., 1929-1937 (Box 64, Folder 1414, Reel 51)
    - Traquair, H. M., 1921-1931 (Box 64, Folder 1415, Reel 51)
    - Treadwell, Alliene W., 1923, 1939 (Box 64, Folder 1416, Reel 51)
    - Tregaskis, James
      See: Series II, Folder 159
    - Trétiakoff, C., 1925 (Box 64, Folder 1417, Reel 51)
    - Trimble, I. Ridgeway, 1938-1939 (Box 64, Folder 1418, Reel 51)
    - Trimble, Theodore F., 1936-1937, undated (Box 64, Folder 1419, Reel 51)
    - Tri-State District Medical Society, 1919-1923 (Box 64, Folder 1420, Reel 51)
    - Trotter, Wilfred, 1915-1939 (Box 64, Folder 1421, Reel 51)
    - Trout, Hugh H., 1927-1939 (Box 64, Folder 1422, Reel 51)
    - Trudeau, Francis B., 1921-1939 (Box 64, Folder 1423, Reel 51)
      See also: Series II, Folder 603
    - Truesdale, Philemon E., 1923-1933 (Box 64, Folder 1424, Reel 51)
    - Trumbull College, 1932-1939 (Box 64, Folder 1425, Reel 51)
    - Truslow, Alice Gray, 1928-1934 (Box 64, Folder 1426, Reel 51)
    - Tudor and Stuart Club, 1923-1934 (Box 64, Folder 1427, Reel 51)
    - Tuffier, T. H. and Mrs., 1923-1934 (Box 64, Folder 1428, Reel 51)
    - Tufts College Medical and Dental School Library, 1939 (Box 64, Folder 1429, Reel 51)
    - Tufts Medical School. William Harvey Society, 1930-1931, 1936 (Box 64, Folder 1430, Reel 51)
    - Turnbull, Hubert M., 1926-1939 (Box 64, Folder 1431, Reel 51)
    - Turner, Alma
    - Turner, George Grey, 1929-1937 (Box 64, Folder 1432, Reel 51)
    - Turner, Philip D., 1927-1928 (Box 64, Folder 1433, Reel 51)
    - Tuttle, Henry Emerson, 1936-1939 (Box 64, Folder 1434, Reel 51)
    - Twin Mutuals, 1920-1931 (Box 64, Folder 1435, Reel 51)
    - Tyson, T. Mellor
      See: Series II, Folder 603
    - Uh-United States C (Box 64, Folder 1436, Reel 51)
    - United States D-University F (Box 64, Folder 1437, Reel 51)
    - University G-Ut (Box 64, Folder 1438, Reel 51)
    - Ulmann, Doris, 1926 (Box 64, Folder 1439, Reel 51)
    - Union Trust Company, 1921-1928 (Box 64, Folder 1440, Reel 51)
    - United States. Bureau of War Risk Insurance
      See: Series II, Folders 912, 913
    - United States. Internal Revenue Service, 1920-1921, 1924-1925 (Box 65, Folder 1441, Reel 51)
    - United States. Surgeon General, 1919-1925 (Box 65, Folder 1442, Reel 51)
      See also: Folder 87
    - United States. Surgeon General, 1926-1931 (Box 65, Folder 1443, Reel 51)
      See also: Folders 87, 559-560; Folders Series II, Folders 192, 874-876
    - United States. Veterans Bureau, 1921-1928 (Box 65, Folder 1444, Reel 51)
      See also: Series II, Folders 20-24, 28, 30
    - United States. War Department, 1918-1919 (Box 65, Folder 1445, Reel 51)
    - United States. War Department, 1923-1926 (Box 65, Folder 1446, Reel 51)
    - University Club of Boston, 1923-1930 (Box 65, Folder 1447, Reel 51)
    - University of Pennsylvania, 1931-1938 (Box 65, Folder 1448, Reel 51)
    - Updike, D. B., 1931-1939 (Box 65, Folder 1449, Reel 51)
      See also: Series II, Folder 17
    - Vac-Vam (Box 65, Folder 1450, Reel 52)
    - Van B-Vand (Box 65, Folder 1451, Reel 52)
    - Vas-Ve (Box 65, Folder 1452, Reel 52)
    - Vi (Box 65, Folder 1453, Reel 52)
    - Vo (Box 65, Folder 1454, Reel 52)
    - Vail, Harris H., 1919-1922, 1931-1935 (Box 65, Folder 1455, Reel 52)
    - Van der Hoeve, J., 1921-1931 (Box 65, Folder 1456, Reel 52)
    - Van der Hoeve, J.: photographs, x-rays, undated (Box 65, Folder 1457, Reel 52)
    - Van Dessel, Arthur
    - Van Wagenen, William P., 1924-1930 (Box 65, Folder 1458, Reel 52)
      See also: Series II, Folders 359, 770, 827
    - Van Wagenen, William P., 1931-1933 (Box 65, Folder 1459, Reel 52)
      See also: Series II, Folders 173-177, 359, 471-475, 770, 827
    - Van Wagenen, William P., 1934-1939 (Box 65, Folder 1460, Reel 52)
      See also: Series II, Folders 173-177, 471-475, 770
    - Vanderbilt University, 1929-1930, 1937 (Box 65, Folder 1461, Reel 52)
    - Vasiliu, D. O.
      See: Series II, Folder 828
    - Verbeek, Ferdinand
    - Verhoeff, F. H.
      See: Series II, Folder 673
    - Viets, Henry R., 1916-1928 (Box 65, Folder 1462, Reel 52)
      See also: Folder 198; Series II, Folders 390, 393, 395, 606, 673, 885
    - Viets, Henry R., 1929-1934 (Box 65, Folder 1463, Reel 52)
      See also: Folder 198; Series II, Folders 393, 395, 606, 673
    - Viets, Henry R., 1935-1937 (Box 65, Folder 1464, Reel 52)
      See also: Series II, Folder 673
    - Viets, Henry R., 1938-1939 (Box 65, Folder 1465, Reel 52)
      See also: Series II, Folders 393, 395, 673
    - Vincent, Clovis, 1928-1939 (Box 66, Folder 1466, Reel 52)
      See also: Series II, Folders 475, 673
    - Vincent, George E.
    - Vincent, Swale, 1914-1924 (Box 66, Folder 1467, Reel 52)
    - Vogel-Wendriner, H. V.
      See: Series II, Folder 243
    - Voynich, Wilfred M.
      See: Series II, Folders 161-165
    - Wa-Wak (Box 66, Folder 1468, Reel 52)
    - Wal (Box 66, Folder 1469, Reel 52)
    - Wan-War (Box 66, Folder 1470, Reel 52)
    - Was-Way (Box 66, Folder 1471, Reel 52)
    - Wea-Weg (Box 66, Folder 1472, Reel 52)
    - Wei-Wen (Box 66, Folder 1473, Reel 53)
    - Wer-Wev (Box 66, Folder 1474, Reel 53)
    - Wh (Box 66, Folder 1475, Reel 53)
    - Wic-Wilk (Box 66, Folder 1476, Reel 53)
    - Will (Box 66, Folder 1477, Reel 53)
    - Wilm-Wilt (Box 66, Folder 1478, Reel 53)
    - Win-Wit (Box 66, Folder 1479, Reel 53)
    - Wo (Box 66, Folder 1480, Reel 53)
    - Wr-Wy (Box 66, Folder 1481, Reel 53)
    - Wade, Henry, 1920, 1930, 1936 (Box 66, Folder 1482, Reel 53)
    - Wadhams, Sanford H., 1935 (Box 66, Folder 1483, Reel 53)
    - Waite, Frederick C., 1924, 1934-1937 (Box 66, Folder 1484, Reel 53)
    - Walcott, Frederic C., 1892, 1916-1939 (Box 66, Folder 1485, Reel 53)
      See also: Series II, Folder 918
    - Walker, Clifford B., 1915-1930 (Box 67, Folder 1486, Reel 53)
    - Walker, Clifford B., 1931-1939 (Box 67, Folder 1487, Reel 53)
    - Walker, I. J.
      See: Series II, Folder 437
    - Walker, M. L.
      See: Series II, Folder 907
    - Wallace, Sir Cuthbert, 1922-1923, 1933 (Box 67, Folder 1488, Reel 53)
      See also: Series II, Folders 810-812
    - Walsh, Joseph, 1932-1937 (Box 67, Folder 1489, Reel 53)
      See also: Series II, Folder 610
    - Walshe, F. M. R., 1925-1933 (Box 67, Folder 1490, Reel 53)
    - Warden, A. A.
      See: Series II, Folder 607
    - Warner, F. J.
      See: Series II, Folders 448-449
    - Warner, Myra
    - Warren, Bentley W.
    - Warren, J. Collins, 1906-1926 (Box 67, Folder 1491, Reel 53)
      See also: Series II, Folders 386, 438, 888
    - Wartenberg, Robert, 1928-1936 (Box 67, Folder 1492, Reel 53)
      See also: Series II, Folder 828
    - Washburn, Frederic A., 1914-1924, 1930 (Box 67, Folder 1493, Reel 53)
      See also: Series II, Folder 245
    - Waverly Press
      See: Folder 1536; Series II, Folder 494
    - Webb, D. A.
      See: Series II, Folder 608
    - Webb-Johnson, Sir Alfred, 1923, 1936, 1939 (Box 67, Folder 1494, Reel 53)
    - Weber, F. Parkes, 1925-1929, 1936-1939 (Box 67, Folder 1495, Reel 53)
    - Wechsler, I. S., 1931-1938 (Box 67, Folder 1496, Reel 53)
    - Weed, C. F., 1921-1933 (Box 67, Folder 1497, Reel 53)
    - Weed, Lewis H., 1914-1923 (Box 67, Folder 1498, Reel 53)
      See also: Series II, Folders 438, 440-442
    - Weed, Lewis H., 1925-1939 (Box 67, Folder 1499, Reel 53)
      See also: Series II, Folders 438, 440-442, 444, 492